B1 Amy is talking about her experience in a tie-dyeing workshop at school.
Listen and complete the notes below.
Yesterday we had a tie-dyeing workshop at school and it was amazing.
We used the traditional method of the Bai people of Dali in Yunnan province and made some wonderful things.
I used a white t-shirt and now it's blue and white with fun patterns.
First I twisted parts of the t-shirt and tied them with string.
Then I put the t-shirt into a big bowl of dye.
The dye got its beautiful blue colour from a special plant.
After a few minutes of moving the t-shirt around in the dye I took it out and let it dry in the sun.
When it was dry I untied the t-shirt and saw the amazing patterns.
I really love my t-shirt and it's great to learn about traditional tie-dyeing.